Wolff, Sidney A. Arbitration Files 5131
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney A. Wolff Arbitration Files
1938-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolff, Sidney A.
5131
34 cubic feet
34 linear ft.
Case files.
Arbitration files involving United Auto Workers (UAW); International Association of Machinists (IAM); Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA); Teamsters (IBT); Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU); Transport Workers Union (TWU); and others.
3338457
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5637: Sidney A. Wolff Additional Arbitration Files 5588: David L. Cole Papers 6004: NAA Additional Records 6441: Sidney A. Wolff Collections
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Wolff, Sidney, 1905-1982.
3338457
- ABC Vending Corporation - American Airlines. (Box 1)
  - ABC Vending Corp. Dist. 65, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Shorthand Reporters w. Accurate Reporting Co., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ace Electrical Contractors -and- Local 199, Industrial Workers of Allied Trade, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Addressomat Inc. - District 65 N.Y. Mediation Board, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dumont Laboratories Inc. - Local 819 Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Air Dispatch Inc. - Local 295 IBT, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Associates, Inc. with IUUAAAIWA, UAW, CIO. Local 201, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Akelex Camera + Instrument Corp. with Local 475, I.U.E., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albany Felt Co - Unlimited Textile WL 439, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albermarle Paper Manufacturing Co. -and- United Papermakers and Paper workers, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Albert Pharmacy - Retail Drug Store Employees Union Local 1199, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Allied Aviation Service International Corp. - Local 504 Air Transport, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allied Fuel - with Local 553, IBT, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Almac Plastics Inc. - Local 815 IBT, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allied New York Services, Inc. Local 553, I.B.T., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers International Local 1 -W- Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Amer. Air Line - T.W.U. -'57-, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Airlines with Transport Workers, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Air Lines, Inc. with Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association International, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Airlines with Air Line Stewards -and- Stewardesses Association, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Airlines Inc. with Transport Workers Union of America, International AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Air Lines - Pilots, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Airlines with T.W.U., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - B, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - C, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - D, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - E, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- American Airlines - American Machine and Foundry. (Box 2)
  - American Bakeries Co. - Local 50 Amer. Bakery Confectionary workers - Med. Bd. 425, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Bosch Arman Corp. - Local 112, ANTE, AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Arma - Local 418, I.U.E., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Arma-Bosch, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arman Cp. + Loc. 460, I.U.E., AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Arma-Bosch, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - American Can Company with United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Chain's Cable Co. Local 4818 - United Steel Workers, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Enka Corp. - TWU, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - F, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Machine + Foundry Corp. with United Automobile Workers, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- American Machine and Foundry - Aurora Plastics. (Box 3)
  - American Sugar Refining Company (The) -Independent Sugar Workers Union, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Optical Co. Local 408, United Optical Workers, 1942-1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Sugar Refining Ind. Sugar Workers Union, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anaconda American Brass - Local 1078 U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anaconda Brass - U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anaconda American Brass -Local 6445- United Steelworkers, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Anaconda - International Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Anaconda Amer. Brass - Local 1078 U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Anaconda Wire + Cable Co. - Local 404 U.E.R,M.W.A., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - HC Anderson Mimeograph Corp. - Local 459 I.U.E.R.M.W., 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ang Wire Service Guild + Associated Press, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ansco Division General with Local 306, ICWU Aniline and Film Corporation, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Apex Machine Mfg. Corp. with Local 475 U.E.R.M.W.A., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Apex Machine Manufacturing Co. - United Electrical Local 475 Arbitration, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Arabian Nights - Actors Equity, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Arma Division - Local 464 I.U.E. AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Arma Corporation with Local 460, International Union of Elec., Radio and Machine Workers., CIO, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Arrow Novelty. Inc. with Local 819, IBT, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Art Steel Co. Local 400 - Sheet Metal, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Associated Former YM-YMHAs of Greater New York - Local 1707 Community + Social Agency Employees Union, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Auburn Transfer Inc. - Local 814 - Teamsters AFL, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Aurora Plastics Corp. Local 815 IBT Med. Bd., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Baker and Taylor Co. - Bloomingdale. (Box 4)
  - I.T. Baker Chemical Co. - Local 8 - 729, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Baker and Taylor Co. - United Office and Prof. Workers Bakers Taylor Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Barbetta Restaurant - Local 1, Dining Room Employees, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Barton's - Arb. Henry Maslia, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bassick Company with Local 1059, IUERMW, CIO, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bassick Co. I.U.E. Local 119 CIO, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Beach Transit Corporation w. Local 252 Transit Workers Union of America C.I.O., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin Alan Co; Albano; Harry Meyers Co. - Local 76B - Furniture Workers, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bergen Machine + Tool Company, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Berger Machine Products, Inc. with District 15, I.A.M., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Berkshire Fine Spinning Associates, Inc., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Berlins Jones Co. Local 192 United Paperworkers Med. Bd., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Berned Optical Messenger Service, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Best Photo Service w. Local 415 United Photographic Employees Union, CIO, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Beverly Storage Co., Inc. - I.B. of T. Local 814, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bloomingdale - Local 3 Wage Case 1946 1st Folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bloomingdales - Local 3 - Grievances, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bloomingdale Bros. - Dist. 65, RNDSU, AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bloomingdale - District 65, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bloomingdale Brothers, Inc with District 65 DPOWA, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bloomingdales -, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bloomingdales - Local 65, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bloomingdales - Distr. 65 (1966) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bloomingdales - Local 3 Wage Case Company Exhibits, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bloomingdale's Local 3 Wage Case Company Exhibits, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bloomingdales - Local 3 Wage Case Company Exhibits, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bloomingdales - Local 3 Threatened Stoppage - 7 Feb. '46, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Bloomingdale. (Box 5)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations, United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America -and- Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Bloomingdale Bros, Inc. -and- Local 3 United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, CIO, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bloomingdale Arbitration Minutes of Hearing May 21, 29. 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc. -and- Local 3 United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, CIO., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc. -and- Local No. 3 United Retail Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bloomingdale - Local 3 Br. Contr., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bloomingdales Local 3 - Reopening, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bloomingdale Local 3 Wage Reopening 1947 2nd Folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Arbitration Bloomingdale Bros. and Local 3 August 29, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Bobby Brooks - Brewers Board of Trade. (Box 6)
  - A.W. Boettcher, Inc. with Amalgamated Local 259, UAW-CIO, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bobbie Brooks - I.L.G.W.U., 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bond Clothes, Inc. Crawford Clothes, Inc. and Ripley Clothes, Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Borden's Farm Products with Local 602 IBT (etc.) AFL, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Borden Company with Local 757 I.B.T., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bordens Farm Products - Local Gov. Milk Wason Drawers + Daisy Employees Med. Bd., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Borden's Farm Products w. Local 20940 Amer. Fed. Of Off Empl., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Borden's Farm Products with Local 602, IBT, AFL, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Bordens Farm Products - and Brunell, Max, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Closed 449, 1940-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Boston + Maine R.R., 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bramhall Deane Co. w. Local 8, Metal Polishers.. Union, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Bran - Lou Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Breakstone Foods Company - Local 277 - I.B.T., 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bremen Pontiac Inc. - Local 259 U.A.W. NY Med Bd., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Brewers Board Trade (IBT), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Beavers Board of Track - Arbitration - WL-26, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Brewers Board of Trade w. Local 69 United Brewery + Soft Drink Workers, CIO, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- British Overseas Airways - Celanese Corporation of America. (Box 7)
  - Briam Manufacturing Corp - United Auto Workers, Local 795 CIO, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bridgeport Lycoming with IUUAAAIWA, UAW, CIO, Local 1010 (Div. of AVCU Mfg.), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - British Overseas Airways Corp., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - BOAC - IAM Oberstein Discharge - 1958 - (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bronx Home News - Newspaper Guild, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - DALU -, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bronx Home News 1st Folder, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratories Association Local 24426 - AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Borough Gas Company with Local 1869, IBEW, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Citizen - Newspaper Guild, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Budd Co. - Ind. Workers Union American Arch. Association, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - C+C Button Company with District 65, RWDSU, CIO, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - C.B.B. Realty Corp (Operating Hotel Lexington Appointments Local 144 Hotel Front Service Employees Union, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Carbona Products Co. - Local 818 - I.B.T., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Celanese Corp. - T.W.U. - Arbitration - S.A.W., 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Celanese Corporation of America with Construction Workers Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia Local 153, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Celanese - Rock Hill S.C. - Local 1093 T.W.U.A., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Exhibits - "Up-Twist" "Down-Twist" (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Celanese Corporation of America with Local 153. United Construction Workers, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Celanese -, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Celanese Corporation of America. (Box 8)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Bridgewater, Virginia) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1191 L 16369 CHA-L-10-56, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Rock Hill, South Carolina) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1093 L-13340 CHA-L-64-54, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Celanese Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America L-19453 PHI-L-210-57, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Celanese Plastic Company and Textile Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Bridgewater, VA) and Local 1191, Textile Workers Union of America L-14395 CHA-L-20-55, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America L-12490 PHI-L-144-54, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): Vacation 1951 and 1954 Contracts 17-Q L-13495 WASH-L- 16-54 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. Thelma Warble of Local 1191, Textile Workers Union of America, and Celanese Corporation of America (Virginia) L-14395 CHA-L-20-55, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia)17-M L-13495 Wash-L-17-54, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Celriver Plant) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1093 L-13973 CHA-L-105-54, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): Preparation Department, 1951 Contract 17-L L-13495 WASH-L-17-54, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): Fannie Hudson 17-O L-13495 Wash-L-17-54, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Narrows Plant) and Untied Construction Workers L-2900 Wash-L-30-47, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1166 L-7721 NY-L-161-51 and L-7801 NY-L-192-51, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Local 1874, Textile Workers Union (Cumberland, Maryland): Separation Pay L-8050 NY-L-23-51, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union Local 1874 L-7646 NYB-L-10-51 and L-7769 NYB-L-16-51, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Local 1874, Textile Workers Union L-7914 NYB-L-19-51 and L-7769 NYB-L-16-51 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Rock Hill, South Carolina) and Local 1093 Textile Workers Union of America L-13913 CHA-L-95-54 and L-13973 CHA-L-105-54, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Rock Hill, South Carolina) and Local 1093, Textile Workers Union of America L-15143 CHA-L-44-55 561, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Textile Workers Union of America Local 1874 versus Celanese Corporation of America: Exhibits (Box 8, Folder 20)
    No date
  - Exhibits (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America and Celanese Corporation of America: New Pay Rate, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Celanese Corporation of America. (Box 9)
  - Local 1874 Textile Workers Union of America and Celanese Corporation of America L-7914 NYB-L-19-51 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America and Celanese Corporation of America: Separation Pay L-8050 BL-23-51, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Celanese Corporation of America versus Textile Workers Union of America Local 1874, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America versus Celanese Corporation of America: "Up-Twist": "Down-Twist", 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America L-6207-PHI-L-44-50 and L-6052-PHI-L-20-50, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union of America L-3064-WAS-L-35-47 (February 24 hearing) and L-3463-WAS-L-5-48 (April 22 hearing) and L-3641-Was-L-9-48 (November 12 hearing), 1948 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Celanese Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America: L-5298-WAS-L-23-49 (August 1949), L-5766-Was-L-35-49 (Cafeteria), and L-5591-Was-L-33-49 (Warp Knit) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 and Celanese Corporation of America (Celcos Plant): Grievance 19-I, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Company Plant, Rock Hill, South Carolina) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1093: CHA-L-55-55, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Celriver Plant) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1093, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - United Mine Workers of America Local 153 and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): Harold Falls Preparation Department 18-L L-13819 WASH-L-24-54, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Textile Workers Union of America Local 1874 and Celanese Corporation of America, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Textile Workers Union of America Local 1874 and Celanese Corporation of America, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America and Celanese Corporation of America: L-7769-NYB-L-16-51, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Celanese Corporation of America versus Textile Workers Union of America, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): William E. Ganoe Suspension - Spinning Department, 1951 Contract 17-K L-13495 WASH-L-17-54, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - United Construction Workers Local 153 (Associated with the United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia): Loula Clarkson Suspension - Spinning Department, 1951 Contract 17-P L-13495 WASH-L-17-54, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Narrows Plant) and United Construction Workers Local 153: L-13819-WASH-L-84-54 Grievances 18-K - 18-O inclusive, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Celanese Corporation of America. (Box 10)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - United Construction Workers (Affiliated with the United Mine Workers of America Local 153) and Celanese Corporation of America, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and Celanese Corporation of America: Exterminator Cases (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and Celanese Corporation of America: Crossing Seniority Lines Case (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and Floyd Boyer and Joseph Gaughan, versus Celanese Corporation of America (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and Oliver G. Lewis, versus Celanese Corporation of America, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and Howard F. Trenum, versus Celanese Corporation of America, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Local 1874, Textile Workers Union of America, and George Knippenberg, versus Celanese Corporation of America, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Celanese Corporation (Rock Hill, South Carolina) and Textile Workers Union of America Local 1093 L-15487 CHA-L-55-55 Numbers 5103, 580, 5146, and 5141, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - United Construction Workers (Affiliated with Local 153, United Mine Workers of America) and Celanese Corporation of America (Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Celanese Corporation of America (Cumberland, Maryland) versus Textile Workers Union of America L-15293-CHI-L-269-55, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Celanese Corporation of America and Textile Workers Union of America Numbers 9817, 9955, 10025, 10476, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Celanese Corporation of America Celriver Plant -and- T.W.U.A., (CIO) Local 1093, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - United Construction Workers, Local 153, U.M.W.A., -and- Celanese Corporation of America, Celco Plant., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Celanese Corporation of America - Columbia Pictures. (Box 11)
  - Textile Workers -and- Celanese Corporation America, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1874 Celanese Corporation of America, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - United Construction Workers, Local No. 153, U.M.W.A., -and- Celanese Corporation of America, Celco Plant, Narrows, Virginia, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1874 Celanese Corporation of America, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Celanese Fibers Co. - Textile Workers of America. Local 1874, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Century Fasteners. Corp. -and Local 1146, RCIA, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Chalmers Knitting Company with Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Chamberlain Corp. United Steelworkers, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Chance Vought Aircraft - Local 893 - UAW, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Chemists Club with Hotel and Club Employees Union, Local 6, AFL, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Chicks Farms - Local 277, IBT, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Childs (200 Fifth Ave.) w. Local 42, Chain Service Restaurant Employees Union, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Chrysler Corporation of America, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - City-Wide Transportation Co., Inc. + Local 348. AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cloud Club w. Hotel + Club Employees Union- Local 6 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Coca Coal Bottling Co. Inc. with Local 812, Soft Drink Workers, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. with Soft Drink Workers Union 812, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Coffee Instant, Inc. - Local 852, I.B.T., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Columbia Combining Dist. 65 - RWDSU, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Columbia Broadcasting Co. with, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Pictures Corporation with Screen Office Professional Employees Guild Columbia Pictures International Corp., 1948 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Columbia Pictures 2nd Folder, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Continental Baking Co. Local 50, Bakery + Confectionary Workers Int. Union Mediation Bd., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - C.B.S., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Columbia with SOPEG, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Craftsmen Welders Inc. - Dupont. (Box 12)
  - American Communications Ass'n. Co. Commercial Cable Co., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Consumers Union, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Concord Paint Co. Inc. -, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cortley Frozen Foods with International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 818, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Craftsmen Welders Inc. - Local 455 - Shopmens Unions, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Crawford Clothiers, Inc. with Local 151 - Window Trimmers and Helpers Union, AFL, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Crescent Furniture Co, et al. - Furniture Workers Union Local 76B, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Actors Equity - Critics Choice, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - B.7. Curry Co. - Local 259, United Auto Workers, C.I.O. - Med. Bd., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Curtiss-Wright Corporation with Aircraft Lodge No. 703, I.A.M. (Propeller Division), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity -and- The Daily Mirror, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 11)